Now,
if you
if we look at each individual one,
right? If you were to look at at
exchange activity, for instance, it's
pretty noisy. And it makes sense
because, you know, Bitcoin when it
spikes or when it it goes to a low,
there's going to be a lot of noise.
But this is an example of like just
because it spikes doesn't mean it's a
bad thing. For instance, it spiked in
December 2018 when the low occurred. It
also spiked going into 2020, again, with
the pandemic low. So, this metric, the
exchange activity score, you can also
see it spiked a lot in January, February
2015 around the market cycle bottom. So,
just because it spikes isn't necessarily
a bad thing.
Some of the whale activity that we're
tracking is more indicative of sort of
showing bottoms, while others might be a
little bit more indicative of showing a
top.